https://www.grandmasfudgefactory.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
At Grandma’s Fudge Factory we respect our customers’ privacy, which is why it is important to us that you understand how we collect, use and disclose information you share with us. We may collect personal and other types of information from you when you interact with Grandma’s Fudge Factory, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Grandma’s Fudge Factory products and services, when you call our sales or support associates and at other times. This information will be used only in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy describes what types of information we collect, how we use the information and for what purposes, to whom we may disclose information, how we protect your information, and your options for managing your information.
This Privacy Policy covers the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) that may be collected by Grandma’s Fudge Factory any time you interact with Grandma’s Fudge Factory such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Grandma’s Fudge Factory products and services, when you call our sales or support associates and at other times. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information and your options for managing your Personal Information.
Information We Automatically Collect
We automatically collect information that does not reflect or reference an individually identifiable user (“Non-Personal Information”) to help us understand how our users use our website. As is true of most commercial websites, our website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, how much time they spend there, etc. We also use cookies and other technologies to improve the quality and functionality of our website and personalize your experience on our website. Most Web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of our website will not function properly if you do so. We also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes, without limitation, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Web browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data.
We may allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our websites. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. For example, we use pixels provided by a third party to track the number of end-user conversions we obtain from its paid search advertising, and a cookie provided by a third party will be placed on the computer of each end-user that clicks on an advertisement so that future advertisements can be targeted to that end-user based on the advertisements clicked on by that end-user. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can contact us at the contact information below and/or visitwww.networkadvertising.org.
Information You Choose To Submit
We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, e-mail address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information (“Personal Information”) only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to make a purchase, register on our website, request a catalog, sign up to receive Grandma’s Fudge Factory e-mails and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to provide such information, you may not be able to access certain areas of our website.
How We Use Personal And Non-Personal Information
We use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as enhancing your experience on our website; performing administration and technical support for our website; notifying you about our new and existing products or services; gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole; and processing and fulfilling your orders and requests.
We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (“Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, marketing services, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, etc. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.
We may combine information you give us online or in our stores. We may also combine such information with publicly available information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes. We may also share or cross-reference, or cause to be shared or cross-referenced, such information, including Personal Information, with unrelated companies you may be interested in so that the companies can directly market their products or services to you.
Although unlikely, at times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose Personal Information. We may also disclose Personal Information if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.
We also may share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with companies affiliated with Grandma’s Fudge Factory. In the event that Grandma’s Fudge Factory is merged, or in the event of a sale or other transfer of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in connection with such transaction.
Managing Your Personal Information
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to update or delete your Personal Information, or opt-out of disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us at:
775-847-0770
Security
We use industry standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties, including using SSL technology for encryption and transmittal of your order information (including your credit card information). However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through our website, and you do so at your own risk.
Children
The safety of children online is very important to us. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a user under the age of 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
Privacy Policy Changes
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page [and the link to this page from our homepage] periodically for changes. Those changes will go into effect on the Effective Date disclosed in the changed Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior Privacy Policies that are inconsistent.
